{
    "attemptedQuizzes": [
        {
            "quiz": {
                "name": "test1",
                "questions": [{
                    "question": "3+9",
                    "correctAnswer": "12",
                    "possibleAnswers": [
                        "12",
                        "1",
                        "2",
                        "3"
                    ]
                }]
            },
            "grade": 1
        },
        {
            "quiz": {
                "name": "test2",
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "1+1",
                        "correctAnswer": "2",
                        "possibleAnswers": [
                            "2",
                            "8",
                            "9",
                            "0"
                        ]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "5+1",
                        "correctAnswer": "6",
                        "possibleAnswers": [
                            "6",
                            "1",
                            "2",
                            "3"
                        ]
                    }
                ]
            },
            "grade": 1
        },
        {
            "quiz": {
                "name": "6",
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "0",
                        "correctAnswer": "1",
                        "possibleAnswers": [
                            "9",
                            "1",
                            "6",
                            "4"
                        ]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "7",
                        "correctAnswer": "1",
                        "possibleAnswers": [
                            "4",
                            "3",
                            "2",
                            "1"
                        ]
                    }
                ]
            },
            "grade": 2
        },
        {
            "quiz": {
                "name": "6",
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "0",
                        "correctAnswer": "1",
                        "possibleAnswers": [
                            "9",
                            "6",
                            "4",
                            "1"
                        ]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "7",
                        "correctAnswer": "1",
                        "possibleAnswers": [
                            "4",
                            "3",
                            "2",
                            "1"
                        ]
                    }
                ]
            },
            "grade": 2
        },
        {
            "quiz": {
                "name": "test2",
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "1+1",
                        "correctAnswer": "2",
                        "possibleAnswers": [
                            "2",
                            "9",
                            "8",
                            "0"
                        ]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "5+1",
                        "correctAnswer": "6",
                        "possibleAnswers": [
                            "1",
                            "3",
                            "2",
                            "6"
                        ]
                    }
                ]
            },
            "grade": 1
        },
        {
            "quiz": {
                "name": "test",
                "questions": [{
                    "question": "0+0",
                    "correctAnswer": "0",
                    "possibleAnswers": [
                        "1",
                        "4",
                        "0",
                        "6"
                    ]
                }]
            },
            "grade": 1
        },
        {
            "quiz": {
                "name": "hello",
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "0+2",
                        "correctAnswer": "2",
                        "possibleAnswers": [
                            "7",
                            "2",
                            "9",
                            "5"
                        ]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "6+1",
                        "correctAnswer": "7",
                        "possibleAnswers": [
                            "2",
                            "1",
                            "7",
                            "3"
                        ]
                    }
                ]
            },
            "grade": 1
        }
    ],
    "allQuizzesMade": [
        {
            "name": "test2",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "1+1",
                    "correctAnswer": "2",
                    "possibleAnswers": [
                        "2",
                        "9",
                        "8",
                        "0"
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "question": "5+1",
                    "correctAnswer": "6",
                    "possibleAnswers": [
                        "1",
                        "3",
                        "2",
                        "6"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "test1",
            "questions": [{
                "question": "3+9",
                "correctAnswer": "12",
                "possibleAnswers": [
                    "12",
                    "1",
                    "2",
                    "3"
                ]
            }]
        },
        {
            "name": "6",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "0",
                    "correctAnswer": "1",
                    "possibleAnswers": [
                        "9",
                        "6",
                        "4",
                        "1"
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "question": "7",
                    "correctAnswer": "1",
                    "possibleAnswers": [
                        "4",
                        "3",
                        "2",
                        "1"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "test",
            "questions": [{
                "question": "0+0",
                "correctAnswer": "0",
                "possibleAnswers": [
                    "1",
                    "4",
                    "0",
                    "6"
                ]
            }]
        },
        {
            "name": "hello",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "0+2",
                    "correctAnswer": "2",
                    "possibleAnswers": [
                        "7",
                        "2",
                        "9",
                        "5"
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "question": "6+1",
                    "correctAnswer": "7",
                    "possibleAnswers": [
                        "2",
                        "1",
                        "7",
                        "3"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}